# Ivan L'olivier

### Senior Full Stack Engineer

Software developer with more than 10 years of experience in the web world. I like feeling ownership of the projects I work on and not only write code but also have a critical view of the product, functionalities, and the business.



ivan.lolivier@gmail.com

Montevideo, Uruguay

in linkedin.com/in/ivan-lolivier

### (+598) 99046538

📾 www.ivanlolivier.me/

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### **Senior FullStack Engineer** ReMatter

10/2020 - Present https://rematter.io/

# Technical Leader - Web developer IUGO

10/2019 - 10/2020 https://iugo.com.uy/

#### Tasks

- Manage development team and do interviews
- Develop Restfull APIs using NodeJs or PHP with Laravel
- Develop SPA using ReactJs or VueJs
- Develop scripts in NodeJs (many scrapers)

## **Technical Leader - Web developer** CodigoDelSur

05/2017 - 10/2019 http://codigodelsur.com/

### - (

- Develop frontend apps using React + Redux + Sagas
- Develop Restfull APIs using NodeJs
- Configure hosting mainly using AWS

# Full Stack Sr. Web Developer DecemberLabs

05/2016 - 05/2017

https://decemberlabs.com/

### Tasks

- Develop Restfull APIs mainly using Laravel
- Develop administrative panels
- Develop FrontEnd pages mainly using AngularJs and ReactJs

## Senior Web Developer AstroPay

03/2012 - 07/2015

https://www.astropay.com/

### Tasks

- Integrating payment methods
- Creating new web pages (usually panels)
- Code optimizations and Security Enhancements

## MAIN SKILLS

Javascript / ES6 React + Redux

HTML5 + CSS3 Node A

PHP + Laravel | SQL / MySQL

## **EDUCATION**

Computer Engineering Universidad de la República

03/2006 - 10/2018 Montevideo, Uruguay

## LANGUAGES

Spanish

Enalish

Portugues

• 0 0 0 0

## INTERESTS

Play football (soccer)

Watch tv series and movies

Run

Research technology

Travel

Go to the gym